export const questions = [
    { question: "UK'S TOP 3 SONGS IN 2020", 
    answers: ["ROSES", "BLINDING LIGHTS", "BEFORE YOU GO", "DANCE MONKEY"],
    right_answer: "BEFORE YOU GO"},

    { question: "COLDPLAY'S ALBUMS", 
    answers: ["A HEAD FULL OF DREAMS", "PARACHUTES", "X&Y", "XYLO MYLOTO"],
    right_answer: "XYLO MYLOTO"},

    { question: "SPOTIFY'S TOP 3 ARTISTS OF 2020", 
    answers: ["DRAKE", "BAD BUNNY", "THE WEEKND", "J BALVIN"],
    right_answer: "THE WEEKND"},

    { question: "MUSE'S ALBUMS", 
    answers: ["AMNESIAC", "ABSOLUTION", "ORIGIN OF SYMMETRY", "SHOWBIZ"],
    right_answer:"AMNESIAC"},

    { question: "SONGS BY JAMES BLAKE", 
    answers: ["BAREFOOT IN THE PARK", "TIMELESS", "RUN", "LIMIT TO YOUR LOVE"],
    right_answer: "RUN"},

    { question: "SPOTIFY'S TOP 3 SONGS OF 2020", 
    answers: ["BAD GUY", "SENORITA", "SUNFLOWER", "SHALLOW"],
    right_answer: "SHALLOW"}, 

    { question: "SONGS BY LANA DEL REY", 
    answers: ["NO TIME TO DIE", "HIGH BY THE BEACH", "SHADES OF COOL", "VIDEO GAMES"],
    right_answer: "NO TIME TO DIE"},

    { question: "SONGS BY ARCTIC MONKEYS", 
    answers: ["505", "WALK AWAY", "BRIANSTORM", "DANCING SHOES"],
    right_answer: "WALK AWAY"},

    { question: "UK'S TOP 3 ALBUMS OF 2021", 
    answers: ["FUTURE NOSTALGIA", "30", "=", "VOYAGE"],
    right_answer: "FUTURE NOSTALGIA"},

    { question: "UK'S TOP 3 ALBUMS OF THE 2010s", 
    answers: ["25", "X", "21", "IN THE LONELY HOUR"],
    right_answer: "IN THE LONELY HOUR"},

]